Brannon Cotherman

Full-Stack Developer

Claims Analyst transitioning into a Developer role after completing my Computer Science degree. Diverse experience in a team setting and coordinating with team members. Over the last five years I have been utilizing many front-end and back-end technologies and have become well versed with many corporate standard technologies like React and MongoDb.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Wilmington University, Wilmington Delaware June 2018 - May 2022

Portfolio

My Website - https://brannondev.io My GitHub - https://github.com/Aceshigh98

Projects

Hashview

This is an application built to monitor mining hardware. It is a fully functional app that shows the status, revenue, and efficiency of active miners. The application is 100% accurate due to Luxor's API. Please use provided credentials to access a demo account.

- Username "demo" Password "!Demo1234!"
- Website https://www.hash-view.com/login
- Tech Stack- React, JavaScript, Node.js, Express, HTML CSS, Docker, Nginx, Linux, JWT

Bitcoin Dashboard

This is a dashboard which is optimized for desktop and mobile devices and provides information such as price network hash rate, market cap, and currency circulation. Data is continuously updated every 5 minutes to show the most up to date statistics.

- Website https://www.aceshighbitcoin.com
- Tech Stack- JavaScript, Node.js, Express, HTML CSS, Docker, Nginx

Experience

Sedgwick

Claims Analyst

December 2022 - May 2024

- Managed and portrayed data for clients and adjusters which enables insight on the extent of the claims.
- Discovered patterns and inconsistencies by utilizing analysis tools to assess the company's liability based on
 policy and investigation findings and was able to achieve accuracy of 95% on claim valuations.
- Evaluated claim values by interpreting data and reports to limit monetary exposure to clients and frequently dropped exposure by 30% based on accurate investigations.

Walmart

Pharmacy Technician

August 2017 - November 2022

- Performed in a fast-paced collaborative environment to provide exceptional medical care to patients in the community.
- Managed team members throughout COVID-19, which led to the store to becoming one of the highest earning stores in the market.
- Quickly achieved conflict resolution with customers and team members which led to a better work environment for all parties.

469-704-6785

brannon98.dev@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/brannon-cotherman

Skills

Languages

JavaScript Typescript HTML CSS

Java

Frameworks/Libraries

React Node.js Tailwind CSS Express Next.js

Databases

MongoDb

VersionControl

Github

Other

Nginx Docker Linux

Oauth

JWT